广播:现在是纽约星期五九点五十七分.
Radio: Three minutes before ten o' clock on a Friday in New York City
我们给你们播放摇滚乐.
and we've got you rockin' and rollin'...
本:我一直忘记,
Ben: I keep forgetting;
这个洲多大才能开车.
how old do you have to be to drive in this state again?
杰森:进去,本,现在.
Jason: Get in side, Ben, now!
麦琪:快点走,先生.
Maggie: Move it, Mister!
杰森:开我们的车兜风!
Jason: Joyriding in our car!
麦琪:无证驾驶.
Maggie: Driving without a licence!
杰森:没有保险.
Jason: Without insurance!
本:别忘了好的消息.
Ben: Let's not forget the good news!
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本:我在宵禁之前回到家.
Ben: I'm home before my curfew.
麦琪:本,我们对你非常,非常失望.你在想什么?
Maggie: Ben, we are very, very disappointed in you.What were you thinking of?
本:而且我一直系着保险带.
Ben: I also wore my seatbelt the whole time.
杰森:好了,本,你被关禁闭了!去你的房间
Jason: That's it Ben, you're grounded!Go to your room!
本:因为系了保险带!我不认为这样的家长负责任.
Ben: For wearing my seat belt!I don't think that's very responsible parenting.
杰森:别再说一句话,本.
Jason: Not another word Ben.
本:我只是想说,我真的抱歉.
Ben: I just wanted to say that I'm really sorry.
我知道我弄糟了,但是我再也不这样了.
I know I screwed up big, and I'll never do it again.
我不知道你们是否还记得,但是作为一个少年十分难受.
I don't know if you guys remember but it's pretty tough being a teen.
麦琪:本,亲爱的,
Maggie: Ben, honey, we love you very much;
我们很爱你;所以我们才会觉得有点失望.
and that's why we're just a little disappointed.
本:谢谢你的理解.那么,为我们烤点热狗怎么样?
Ben: Thanks for understanding.So, how about roasting us some hot dogs?
杰森:我说,回你房间.
Jason: I said, go to your room!
本:我还要关禁闭!
Ben: I'm still grounded!
麦琪:是,除非我们想到了别的处罚.
Maggie: Well, until we can think of the rest of your punishment.
本:我不接受,我拥抱了你们.
Ben: I don't get it; I hugged you guys and everything.
杰森:我很感动.回你房间去.
Jason: I was moved.Go to your room.
本:这个跟电视上的方式不同.
Ben: This isn't the way it happens on TV.
麦琪:这和电视有什么关系?
Maggie: What's TV got to do with this?
本:在每个家庭,在每部电视剧,
Ben: In every family, on every TV show, when the kids mess up,
孩子闯了祸,
all they have to do is hug before the last commercial!
他们所要做的是在广告前拥抱一下!你们在哪呢?
Where the heck have you been?
杰森:那么,你看这有摄像机?
Jason: Well, do you see any cameras here?Do you see any lights?
你看见灯光吗?这不是电视,本.
This is not TV, Ben.This is the real world!
这是现实世界!问题没那么容易解决.
Problems just aren't solved that easy.
本:我知道了,爸爸;那就是他们有两个版本.
Ben: I know, Dad; that's why they have two-parters.
杰森:本!
Jason: Ben!
本:巴特 辛普森把厕所弄得一团糟,他也没有被送进他的房间.
Ben: Bart Simpson blew up a toilet, and he wasn't sent to his room.
杰森:他是卡通人物!
Jason: He's a cartoon!
本:是的,想想对我们人来说不就很容易了吗.
Ben: Yeah, so think how easy it should be for us humans.
杰森:我要你回到你的房间……我要你想想你做错了什么.
Jason: I want you to go to your room...
I want you to think about what you did wrong.
本:我告诉你错在什么地方;我在这个现实世界,
Ben: I'll tell you what's wrong;
不是在电视里.
me being stuck here in the real world and not on TV.
本:我做什么了,而且为什么它是错的.我被关了.
Ben: What did I do, and why it was wrong.I got caught.
这可能也是错.电视上的声音:停!停!
That's probably wrong too.Voice from above: Cut!Cut!Cut!
停!再来一遍,从开头.
Once again, from the top!
本:嘿,你是谁?
Ben: Hey, who are you?
电影工作人员:特殊效果.
Film crew: Special Effects.
制片:呃……我们得再来一遍;停顿时间太长了.你忘了台词了?
Producer: Err...we're gonna have to do that again; it's way to big of a
pause.Did you forget your line
本:什么台词?你是谁?这里发生什么了?
Ben: What line?Who are you?What's going on here?
制片:别耍滑头了;导演心情不好.
Producer: Don't play games; the director's in a bad mood.
Director: In a very bad mood.Every one whose name begins with a G is
fired.Mmmm
本:嘿,这房间的其他部分在哪里呢?我在哪?
Ben: Hey, where's the rest of my bedroom?Where am I?
制片:见西维尔一家,片头场景.第二.记住,
Producer: Meet The Seavers, opening scene.Take two.
你的第一句台词要说的很温柔.五,四,三……
Remember, your first line is said very softly.In five, four, three...
本:啊!!!!
Ben: Aarrgghh!!!!
本:啊!你们所有人,出去!快点,
Ben: Aarrgghh!All of you, out!Come on, get out of my room!Get back!
从我房间出去!快点!从我房间出去!.
Get out of my room!
制片:杰里米!杰里米,你在让我难堪.
Producer: Jeremy!Jees, you're making me look bad.
本:妈妈!爸爸!这里发生什么了?
Ben: Mom!Dad!What is going on here?
制片:我正是我想知道的,
Director: That's what I want to know, Jeremy.
杰里米.两小时以后我们就开演了,
We're doing a show here in two hours and this Emmy winning director doesn't
这个Emmy奖最佳导演不不需要这种痛苦.
need this grief.
本:为什么你们叫我杰里米,他是谁?是上帝?
Ben: Why are you calling me Jeremy?Who is that?Is that God?
制片:对我而言他是的.
Producer: He is to me.
导演:苏珊!苏珊,给杰里米最好提醒一下台词.
Director: Susan!Susan, give Jeremy his line for the last time.
苏珊:我得告诉爸爸妈妈,我很抱歉,
Susan: I've got to tell Mom and Dad how sorry I am and how much I
但是我非常地爱他们.
love them.
本:这太奇怪了.
Ben: This is too weird.
苏珊:告诉我这些.
Susan: Tell me about it.
本:爸爸!爸爸!
Ben: Dad!Dad!Boy, am I glad to see you.
真高兴我看到你了.我一直到处在找你.发生什么事情了?
I've been looking all over for you.What is happening?
杰森:不,嘘嘘.现在你去告诉迪斯尼乐园的人,我不能出席那个剪彩活动了,我得和摩根参加接力游行.
Jason: No, Shh shh.Now you've got to tell the Disney people I cannot make
that ribbon cutting on the fifth.
I got the Passover Parade with Morgan Fairchild
本:爸爸,我必须和你谈谈.
Ben: Dad, I gotta talk to you.
杰森:好的,说吧.
Jason: Yeah, go ahead.
本:爸爸,听着,在这一些很奇怪的事情发生了.
Ben: Dad, look something really weird is going on here.
我们家,哦,像我们的家,
Our house, well, it's like our house, but it isn't.
可又不是.还有这么多怪人.我想我要发疯了.
There's all these strange people.I think I'm losing my mind.
杰森:呃……不,不,不!
Jason: Err...No, no, no!
我很清醒,孩子;我说的很明确,不,去新的比赛,
I was very clear babe; I said a definite, no, to the new match game,
和确切的,是的,去建的好莱坞广场.
and a definite, yes, to the new Hollywood square.
本:爸爸,你能放下电话吗……我在这快死了.
Ben: Dad, can you get off the phone...I'm dying here.
杰森:杰里米,你不去找你真正的家庭来帮你?
Jason: Jeremy, don't you have your real family to help you with that?
本:你是我的真的家人!你也叫我杰里米.
Ben: You are my real family!You called me Jeremy too.
杰森:对,我这么叫的.这是你的名字.一年半来我一直是这么叫你的.这是你的名字,是不是?你叫什么名字?
Jason: Yes, I did.That's your name.That's what I've been calling you for six
seasons.That is your name isn't it?What's your name
本:爸爸!
Ben: Dad!
杰森:我不是你的爸爸.我在电视里演你爸爸.会见西维尔一家!记得吗?
Jason: I'm not your dad.I play your father on television.Meet the Seavers!Remember
本:啊?
Ben: Huh?
杰森:我不是不在乎,你像我的亲生儿子……我……不!这是中心广场,否则我步行.
Jason: It's not like I don't care about you like me real son...I do...No!It's centre square, or I walk.
本:不,不,爸爸,这错了.
Ben: No, no, Dad, this is wrong.Come on, we are not a TV family.
行了,我们不是电视里的一家.我们是真的一家子.
We are a real family.
杰森:那么,为什么他们不替换欧克尔?
Jason: Well, why don't they just bump Urkel?
本:妈妈!妈妈!
Ben: Mom!Mom!
麦琪:那是什么,亲爱的?
Maggie: What is it, honey?
本:我不知道.我什么也不知道.
Ben: I don't know.I don't know anything.I am going nuts here.
我在这要发疯了.
It seems to me that someone has gone to a lot of trouble to mess with
这似乎对我来说,有人用很多烦恼的事情把我脑子搅浑了.
my head.
阿什莉:妈妈……妈妈!
Ashley: Mom...Mom!
麦琪:什么,亲爱的?
Maggie: What, honey?
阿什莉:我可以今晚呆在黛丝瑞家吗?
Ashley: Can I please spend the night at Desree's tonight.
我保证我不会待的很迟.
I promise I won't stay up late...
本:妈妈,这是谁?为什么她叫你,妈妈?
Ben: Mom, who is this?Why's she calling you, Mom?
麦琪:哦,你知道我的女儿,阿什莉.
Maggie: Oh, you know my daughter, Ashley.
本:我姐姐!
Ben: My sister!
麦琪:我女儿.
Maggie: My daughter.
本:我姐姐.
Ben: My sister!
麦琪:我女儿.
Maggie: My daughter.
本:不,阿什莉不是你的女儿.开萝尔和克莉丝是的.
Ben: No, Ashley's not your daughter, Carol and Chrissy are.
麦琪:哦,哦,
Maggie: Oh, oh, they're my TV daughters.Ashley's my real daughter.
她们是我在电视里的女儿.阿什莉是我的现实生活里的女儿.你应该知道电视和现实生活的区别.
You do know the difference between TV and real life.
本:我身上到底发生了什么?
Ben: What's happening to me?
阿什莉:想想吧,我曾经以为你很聪明.
Ashley: And to think, I used to think you were hot.
汉斯:嗨,大美女!
Hans: Hey, gorgeous!
麦琪:哦,嗨,亲爱的.
Maggie: Oh, hi honey.
汉斯:宝贝.
Hans: Baby.
本:嗨!
Ben: Hey!
汉斯:唉!
Hans: Ay!
麦琪:杰里米 米勒,你发生什么事情了?
Maggie: Jeremy Miller, what's gotten into you?
本:妈妈,你在干什么?爸爸就在那.
Ben: Mom, what are you doing?Dad's right over there.
麦琪:哦,他只是我电视上的丈夫,
Maggie: Oh, he is only my TV husband.Hans is my real life...friend.
汉斯是我现实生活的……朋友.现在你必须道歉.
Now you should apologise.
本:相信我,我再也不开家里的车去兜风了.
Ben: Believe me, I will never joy-ride in the family car again.
麦琪:哦,杰里米,我们能不能过会对台词?
Maggie: Oh, Jeremy, can we run these lines a little later?
开萝尔:来人叫个护士;那傻蛋又这样了!
Carol: Somebody call a nurse; the klutz did it again!
本:你认识我.
Ben: You know me.
开萝尔:离我远点,你让我恶心.
Carol: Get away from me, you disgust me.
本:当然我会,我是你弟弟.
Ben: Of course I do, I'm your brother.
开萝尔:我没有兄弟.我有几个姐妹.
Carol: I don't have any brothers.
他们都十分聪慧.
I have several sisters though; all of whom are mighty talented.
本:开萝尔,听着,
Ben: Carol, look, I know we haven't gotten along and I know we have our
我知道我们我们没有相处过,我知道我们有不同之处,
differences, but I have to ask you a favour...Stop kidding with me!
但我不得不请你帮忙……别在开我的玩笑了!我不知道我能否还能忍受一分钟.
I don't know if I can take it for another minute.
开萝尔:凯文,我下午完事了吧?
Carol: Kevin, am I done for the afternoon?
制片:是的,我们只有到正式演出时才需要你.
Producer: Sue, we don't need you till the audio show.
开萝尔:啊!开心.
Carol: Aha!Yippee.
本:好的,我闭上眼睛,等我睁开眼睛,我就会回到自己房间了.
Ben: OK, I'm gonna close my eyes and when I open 'em back up,
一,二,三.
I'm gonna be in my room.One.Two.Three.
克莉丝:你在干什么?
Chrissy: What the heck are you doing?
本:克莉丝,告诉我你是克莉丝.
Ben: Chrissy, tell me you're Chrissy.
克莉丝:我是克莉丝.但是这个夏天的八个星期,我就变成安妮.(唱歌)太阳就要出来,明天.跟你打赌,明天是晴天.只要想想明天,擦去烦恼和忧伤,直到什么都没有.当我想象那灰色的天…….
Chrissy: I'm Chrissy.But for eight weeks this summer, I'm gonna be Annie!(Singing) The sun'll come out, tomorrow.Bet your bottom Dollar that tomorrow there'll be sun.Just thinking about tomorrow cleans away the cobwebs and the sorrow, till there's no more.When I think of the day that's grey and...
本:啊!
Ben: Aarrghh!
克莉丝:(唱歌)……孤独的.我只是伸出我的下巴和牙齿,说.各位!
Chrissy: (singing) ...lonely.I just stick out my chin and grin and say.
明天,我爱你们!明天你们只有离开一天!明天!明天……
Everybody!Tomorrow
I love you!Tomorrow you're only a day away!Tomorrow!Tomorrow
本:嗨,迈克在哪?
Ben: Hey, where's Mike?Mike Seaver.Chauffeur: Over there.
迈克 西维尔.司机:在那.他认为他可以欺骗我.
He thinks he can trick me.
迈克:谢谢你的支持.回见.
Mike: Thanks for the support.See you later.
本:是还是不是,你是我哥哥,
Ben: Yes or no,
还是假扮我哥哥的演员?
are you my brother or are you just an actor pretending to be?
迈克:又来了?
Mike: Come again?
凯特:午饭好了,小甜心?
Kate: Ready for lunch, sweetheart?
迈克:哦,嗨,是呀,听起来不错.你想加入我们吗?
Mike: Oh, hey, yeah, sounds great.You wanna join us?
本:凯特,你也在这.
Ben: Kate, you're here too.
迈克:你在说什么呢?你知道切尔西.
Mike: What are you talking about?You know Chelsea.
本:谁是切尔西?
Ben: Who's Chelsea?
凯特:我.
Kate: Me.
本:不,你是凯特.
Ben: No, you're Kate.
迈克:不,不,不.在电视上,她是凯特,但是在现实生活中她是我女朋友.
Mike: No, no, no.On TV, she's Kate, but in real life she's my girlfriend.
本:同一个人.
Ben: It's the same person!
迈克:是的.难道你没有看"娱乐今晚"?
Mike: Yeah.Don't you watch Entertainment Tonight?
本:迈克,如果你还坚持那些的话,
Ben: Mike, if you're in there somewhere, please, you've got to help me.
请你,你一定要帮助我.
I said that life was better on TV,
我说生活比电视好,不知道什么原因我就被这愚蠢的电视给迷住了.
and somehow I got stuck on this stupid TV show.
迈克:嗨,如果你对电视秀不感兴趣,
Mike: Hey, if you're unhappy with the TV show,
也许你应该和你的经纪人谈谈.
maybe you should be talking with your agent.
本:我没有经纪人.
Ben: I don't have an agent.
凯特:那,你真的不该惊讶,你的角色太小.
Kate: Well, you really shouldn't be surprised your parts gotten so small.
本:嗨,我只是想离开这里!
Ben: Hey, I just wanna get out of here!
迈克:嗨,别这么大声.
Mike: Hey, not so loud.Remember what happened to Shelly Long?
记得莎莉朗发生的事情吗?哦,这样发生在许多儿童演员身上的事情我见多了.
Oh, I've seen this happen to so many kid actors.
本:我要回家去.
Ben: I've got to go home.
司机:你可以,孩子.
Chauffeur: You got it kid.
本:你会开车送我.
Ben: You'll drive me.
司机:你认为是什么呢,他们付钱给我站在这里吃圈饼?
Chauffeur: What do you think, they pay me to stand here and eat doughnuts?
本:好极了!行!是的,我需要去长岛.
Ben: Great!Alright!Yeah, I need to go to Long Island.
司机:我想你要回家.
Chauffeur: I thought you wanted to go home.
本:我就是住在那里!罗宾汉街15号!
Ben: That's where I live!Fifteen Robin Hood's Lane!
司机:你搬家了!
Chauffeur: You moved!
本:不,我没搬家.
Ben: No I didn't move!
司机:放松,放松,你是老板.儿童演员!
Chauffeur: Easy, easy, you're the boss.Kid actors!
本:行了,这是我的街区!
Ben: Alright, this is my street!
司机:我们到这里了,罗宾汉街15号.
Chauffeur: Here we are, Fifteen Robin Hood lane.
本:这不可能正确.
Ben: This can't be right.
加油人:下午好!加满它?
Gas man: Afternoon!Fill her up?
本:请问,这是罗宾汉街15号吗?
Ben: Excuse me, is this fifteen Robin Hood Lane?
加油人:你是国税局的?
Gas man: You with the IRS?
本:不是.
Ben: No.
加油人:是的,就是它.
Gas man: Yes, it is.
本:我家在哪?我住在罗宾汉街15号.
Ben: Where's my house?I live at fifteen Robin Hood lane.
加油人:除非你睡在油桶上.
Gas man: Not unless you been sleeping on the lube racks.
本:我发生了什么事情?我在哪里?没有人知道我是谁?
Ben: What's happening to me?Where am I?Doesn't anybody know who I am?
加油人:嗨,你控制你自己,我肯定认识你.
Gas man: Hey, hold your horses, I do know you.
本:你认识!哦,谢天谢地!
Ben: You do!Oh, thank God!
加油人:是的,你是"与西维尔一家相识"里面的小孩,杰里米 莫勒.
Gas man: Yeah, you're that kid on Meet the Seavers, Jeremy Muller.
嗨,我能不能替我的孙女跟你要一下你的签名?
Hey can I have your autograph for my little granddaughter?Her name's Bub.
她的名字叫巴布.我在外面有些湿水泥,你可以脱掉你的鞋.
I've got some wet cement outside if you'd like to take your shoes off.
司机:我对此不担心,
Chauffeur: I wouldn't worry about it kid;
孩子;有些晚上我也会忘记我住在哪里.
some nights I forget where I live too.
本:嗨,我知道了.带我去我奶奶欧玛的寓所,在曼哈顿.
Ben: Hey, I know.Take me to my grandma Urma's apartment in Manhattan.
司机:她那里有洗手间吗?
Chauffeur: Has she got a bathroom?
制片:杰里米,你去哪里了?
Producer: Jeremy, where've you been?The audience is here.
观众都在这.我们都准备开始了.
We're all set for the show.
本:听着,你们找错了人.我不能表演.
Ben: Look, you've got the wrong guy.I can't act!
制片:没关系,编剧也不会写.
Producer: It's OK, the writers can't write.
本:嗨,你们在干什么?
Ben: Hey, what are you doing?I can't act!You've got the wrong guy.
我不会表演!你们找错人了.我不会比表演!
I cannot act!Let me go!
主持人:好,谁从农村来?哦,对,对……
Host: OK, who's from out of town?Oh, yeah, yeah...
观众:喔!
Audience: Woo!!
主持人:嗨,等等!女士们,先生们,这是本 西维尔,杰里米 米勒!
Host: Hey, wait!Ladies and gentlemen, there's Ben Seaver, Jeremy Miller!
制片:听着,对聪明孩子只说一句;你把今天的预言搞砸了.猜想谁会不高兴.
Producer: Look, a word to the wise kid; you screwed up today's rehearsal.Guess who's not happy.
导演:我.
Director: Me.
制片:快点!快点!
Producer: Come on!Come on!
我要你进那辆车,
I want you to get in that car and be funny,
开开心心的,就像你的生活就依靠这个.
like your life depended on it.
本:但是我甚至不知道这里发生了什么.
Ben: But I don't even know what's going on here.
制片:哦,上帝.
Producer: Oh, God.You've been out joy-riding, you're sneaking in the house,
你出去兜风,你偷偷进入屋子,你父母教训了你.
your parents bust you.
本:但是我已经经历过了.
Ben: But I already been through that.
制片:很好!也许你可以表演这个.
Producer: Good!Maybe you can play it then.
本:等一下;这就是整个事情怎么样开始的.
Ben: Wait a minute; this is how this whole thing began.
制片:与西维尔一家相识.第140集.好好表演,伙计!
Producer: Meet the Seavers.Episode number one forty.Have a good show gang!
五,四,三,二……
In five, four, three, two...
本:太奇怪了.
Ben: This is too weird.
我一直忘记这个州多大岁数才能开车?
I keep forgetting, how old do you have to be to drive in this state?
杰森:进去,本,现在!
Jason: Inside Ben, now!
麦琪:快点,先生!
Maggie: Move it Mister!
这就是整个事情怎么样开始的.
Ben: This is how this whole thing started.
导演:快点,杰里米!你难道不是应该出来进厨房了?
Director: Come on Jeremy!Were you not supposed to exit to the kitchen?
本:行,我就那样做的.
Ben: That's right, I did do that.
导演:我不高兴.
Director: I am not amused.
麦琪:杰里米,你怎么了?
Maggie: Jeremy, what's gotten in to you?Just...
就……就像你知道的,
just you know, just like we rehearsed;
就像我们预演的;只要进入厨房,然后等待你的信号.
just go into the kitchen and wait on your mark.
五,四,三,二!
Producer: In five, four, three, two!
本:什么信号?
Ben: What's a mark?
杰森:开我们的车去兜风!
Jason: Joyriding in our car!
麦琪:无证驾驶.
Maggie: Driving without a license!
杰森:没有保险.
Jason: Without insurance!
本:我在宵禁之前回到家.
Ben: Errm...I am back before my curfew.
麦琪:本,我们对你非常,非常失望.你在想什么?
Maggie: Ben, we are very, very disappointed in you.What were you thinking of?
本:而且我一直系着保险带.
Ben: I also wore my seatbelt the whole time.
杰森:好了,本,你被关禁闭了!去你的房间
Jason: That's it Ben, you're grounded!Go to your room!
本:走哪边?
Ben: Which way would that be?
麦琪:你不是真的去,你道歉.
Maggie: You don't really go, you apologise.
本:哦,行.
Ben: Oh right.Errm...I'm sorry.
呃……真的抱歉.我知道我弄糟了,但是我再也不这样了.
I know I screwed up big and I'll never do it again.
我不知道你们是否还记得,但是作为一个少年十分难受.
You guys know how hard it is to be a teenager.
麦琪:本,亲爱的,
Maggie: Ben, we love you very much;
我们很爱你;所以我们才会觉得有点失望.
that's why we were just a little disappointed.
杰森:哦,没什么,
Jason: Oh, what the heck, we forgive you!
我们原谅你!为你们烤点热狗怎么样?
How about roasting up your man a couple of hotdogs?
麦琪:哦,没有什么我更愿意做的了.哦,
Maggie: Oh, there is nothing else I would rather do.
别担心,小东西,他说热狗.
Oh, don't worry Spot, he said hotdogs!
本:你们怎么回事?
Ben: What's with you people?
杰森:这就叫定格.
Jason: This is the freeze frame.
本:不,不,等等.但是你们不会因为一个愚蠢的拥抱就接受我的道歉.你应该关我禁闭.
Ben: No, no, wait.But you would not accept my apology with a stupid hug.You'd ground me.
杰森:别动.你破坏了定格.
Jason: Stop moving.You're running the freeze frame.
本:我不在乎什么定格呢!行了,这些都错了!这根本不是所想像的那样.
Ben: I don't care about the freeze frame!Come on, this is all wrong!This is not how it's supposed to be.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh.
杰森:怎么了?我们在排练或者什么地方做了一点改变?
Jason: What's going on?Did we change this bit in rehearsal or something?
导演"我们绝对肯定没有!
Director: We most certainly did not!
本:在现实生活中,事情根本不是这样的.
Ben: In real life, this is not how it is at all.
杰森和麦琪:这不是现实生活,这是电视,杰里米.
Jason and Maggie: This isn't real life, this is television, Jeremy!!
本:有人吗,快点,
Ben: Somebody, come on, you've got to help me please!
你们得帮帮我!我要离开这里!我要回家!
I have to get out of here!I have to get home!
制片:杰里米!
Producer: Jeremy!
本:有没有人帮我?
Ben: Is there anyone who can help me?
制片:过来.
Producer: Come here.
本:你过来,请你了.
Ben: You come here, please.
我不知道你,但是你看起来想真实的人,我……
I don't know you but you look like a real person, I...
汉斯:杰里米 米勒,各位.他表演的就像真实生活!
Hans: Jeremy Miller everyone.He makes it just like real life!
制片:过来!
Producer: Come here!
本:离我远点!
Ben: Get away from me!
迈克:哇!哇!哇!凯文!凯文!凯文!我想我可以帮忙,就让我和他单独待一会.
Mike: Wow.Wow!Wow!Kevin!Kevin!I think I can help, just let me have a minute alone with him.
制片:性,柯克,无论你说什么.
Producer: Alright, Kirk, whatever you say.
本:听着……
Ben: Listen...
迈克:嘘.行了,我们不能在这里谈话.
Mike: Shh.Come on, we can't talk here.
本:听着,无论你是谁,我不……
Ben: Look, whoever you are, I don't...
迈克:本,本,本,行了!是我,迈克.
Mike: Ben, Ben, Benny, come on!It's me, Mike.
本:迈克!那么,我没有疯!
Ben: Mike!So, I'm not crazy!
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yes.
本:我怎么知道真的是你.迈克,真是你.
Ben: Wait a minute, how do I know it's really you?Mike, it is you!!
迈克:是我.
Mike: Yeah.
本:快点,我们得离开这里,快!
Ben: Come on, we have to get out of here, please!
迈克:本,本,行了.你是大人了.现在这就是你的世界.
Mike: Benny, Benny, come on.Be an adult.Now this is your world now.
本:啊?
Ben: Huh?
迈克:是的.本,
Mike: Yes.Ben, you're not crazy.
你没有疯.好了,五年前,
OK, five years ago,
我没有学习,而是睡觉了,至从那是我就被骗到这里.
I fell asleep instead of studying and I have been trapped here ever since.
是呀,你不会相信他们让我做的一切事情.
Yeah, you wouldn't believe the stuff they've made me do.
本:无路出去!
Ben: There's no way out!
迈克:你不想想,如果有,
Mike: Don't you think if there was, I'd find one?
我肯定找到?你不想想,我希望在电视里长大一点?
Don't you think, I'd like to grow up a little on the show?
表演的更加成熟一点?也许甚至长一些胡须!但是不,
Act a bit more mature?Maybe even grow some facial hair!
他们不让你!他们拥有你!
But no, they won't let you!They own you!
本:不是我!没有人拥有我!
Ben: Not me!Nobody owns me!
迈克:嗨,你逃不掉的!他们知道你住在什么地方!他们布的景!
Mike: Hey, you can't escape!They know where you live!They built the set!
保安:我去这边.你和狗去湿地!
Security: I'll go this way.You and the dogs take the swamp!
导演:如果你们找到他,带他来见我.
Director: When you find him bring him to me.
如果你们找不到他,让佛瑞德 塞维基听电话.
And if you can't find him, get me Fred Savage on the phone.
如果他也找不到,那就找欧克尔.
If you can't find him, bring me Urkel.
导演:嗨.
Director: Hi.
导演:这是导演在说话.
Director: This is the Director talking.
你们别去理那个在麦克风里喊叫的人.
Pay no attention to that man shouting in the microphone!
本:你是那个伟大和强大的导演!你是每个人害怕的导演!
Ben: You're the great and powerful director!
你是小男人.
You're the guy everybody's afraid of!You're a weenie!
导演:求你了,别说了.求你了,求你了!
Director: Please, don't tell.Please, please!
本:(用导演的麦克风)他是个小男人!
Ben: (with director's microphone) He's a weenie!
导演:安静.
Director: Be quiet.
本:大伙,我不相信这一切;这是个十足的假冒……骗局!
Ben: Man, I can't believe this; this is all phony...tricks!
这里什么都不是真实的.
None of this is real!
导演:听着,我不认为你看到了这里的一切场景,杰里米.
Director: Look, I don't think you're getting the whole picture here, Jeremy.
本:停止表演.我哥哥告诉我.我不是杰里米,我是本 西维尔.
Ben: Cut the act.My brother told me.I'm not Jeremy, I'm Ben Seaver.
导演:那么你知道了.但是这不会改变任何东西.
Director: So you know.Well that doesn't change anything.
本:会,会改变!我要出去.
Ben: Yes it does!I want out.
导演:对不起,没人可以出去.
Director: Sorry, no can do.
本:为什么不能出去?
Ben: Why not?
导演:那么,如果我让你走,
Director: Well, if I let you out, I've got to let everybody out.
我就不得不让每个人走.迈克是下一个,然后是歌曲伴舞的小孩子.
Mike next and that little song a dance kid.
本:但是我不想成为在电视上的.我需要真实的家庭.
Ben: But I don't want to be on TV.I want a real family.
导演:之前你不是这么说的.
Director: That's not what you said before.
本:什么时候?
Ben: When?
导演:苏珊!
Director: Susan!
苏珊:第五页,在厨房里.
Susan: Page five, in the kitchen.
我告诉你什么地方错了;我在现实生活中被陷在这里,而不是在电视中.
I'll tell you what's wrong; I'm stuck here in the real world, and not on TV.
本:不,不,我肯定这样说了.
Ben: Oh, no, I did say that.
导演:你当然说了.
Director: You certainly did.
本:然后我回到我的房间,整个噩梦就开始了.
Ben: And then I went to my room, and this whole nightmare started.
导演:嗨,这没那么坏,
Director: Hey, it's not so bad, Ben.
本.
Let me explain how TV families work;
让我告诉你电视里的家庭是个什么样;你没有一个问题不能在半个小时之内解决的,
you never have a problem you can't solve in a half hour, you don't get sick,
你不会生病,你永远不去洗手间……女孩认为你可爱,
you never go to the bathroom...
而且你一直有有趣的事情讲述,多亏了,
girls think you're cute and you always have something funny to say,
而且这是我们的秘密……编剧.
thanks to, and this is our secret...the writers.
本:嗨,他们对我的房间干了些什么?
Ben: Hey, what are they doing to my room?
导演:拆了.如果你不继续演,
Director: Taking it down.If you're not gonna do the show, we gotta move on.
我们继续.下周我们继续进行一个非常特别……我们要重演.
Next week we gonna do a very special...We could show a re-run.
本:我要回到那里.
Ben: I gotta get back there.
导演:本,我对你讲话还没有完呢.
Director: Ben, I'm not finished talking to you yet.
导演:拦住他!别让他靠近他的房间!拦住他!
Director: Stop him!Don't let him near his room!Stop him!
本:不,什么都别碰.回去!走开!
Ben: No, don't touch any of it.Back!Get away!Don't touch any of it!
什么都别碰!我开始数三,然后我推开被子,
I'm gonna count to three, then I'm gonna pull off the covers,
我要回家,我要被关禁闭,我会很高兴.一,
I'm gonna be home, I'm gonna be grounded and I'm gonna be so happy.
二,三!啊!
One, two, three!Ah!
没有墙,没有灯,没有相机,没有小男人导演!!
No missing wall, no lights, no cameras, no weenie directors!!Ha!Yes!
哈!是!我想我可以开车出去庆祝!
I think I'll take the car out and celebrate!No, no, that would be wrong.
不,不,那样会犯错的.你们知道我是谁吗?
Anybody do you know who I am?
开萝尔:我愿意和你没有关系.
Carol: Someone I'd rather not be related to.
本:你承认我们有关系!我爱你.
Ben: You admit we're related to!I love you.
开萝尔:啊!现在我又得去洗个澡了.
Carol: Arrgh!Now I'm gonna have to shower again.
麦琪:本,你怎么了?
Maggie: Ben, what's gotten into you?
本:我已经想了一夜.
Ben: I've been thinking all night.
杰森:很好.
Jason: Good.
本:是的,我错了.现实生活比电视好多了.
Ben: Yeah, I was wrong.The real world is much better than TV.
杰森:什么?那不是你应该想的.
Jason: What?That's not what you're supposed to be thinking about.
你应该想想为什么不该开车.
You're supposed to be thinking about why you shouldn't drive.
本:是吗?
Ben: I was?
麦琪:是的,本.
Maggie: Yes Ben.
本:那么,我没有必要想这些.
Ben: Well, I don't have to think about that.
我在做之前,我就知道这是错的.
I knew it was wrong before I did it.
那就是为什么我偷偷溜进来,
That's why I was sneaking in, but you guys don't have to get upset,
但是你们没有必要生气,欢迎你们为此惩罚我.
you are welcome to punish me for it.
杰森:哦,我们会的,我们会的.
Jason: Oh, we will Ben, we will.
本:很好.
Ben: Great.
杰森:没有通知的话,禁闭继续.
Jason: The grounding remains until further notice.
本:成交.
Ben: Deal.
杰森:暂停一个月的零用钱.
Jason: The allowance is suspended for a month.
本:好极了!
Ben: Super!
杰森:你每周都要擦洗车子,
Jason: You will wash that car every weekend until you show some
指导你表现出责任心.
responsibility.
本:很好.
Ben: That's terrific.
麦琪:你很高兴接受这些!
Maggie: You're happy with all this!
本:是的,我只是高兴你没有去吻那个男人,名字叫汉斯.
Ben: Yeah, I'm just glad you're not kissing a man named Hans.
杰森:汉斯!
Jason: Hans!
本:而且我也高兴你没有跟摩根游行.
Ben: And I'm glad you're not parades with Morgan Fairchild.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: Pardon me.
本:听着,我知道这不会改变一件事情,但是……我爱你们.我爱你们.
Ben: Look, I know this won't change a thing, but...I love you.I love you.
杰森:谁是汉斯?
电视(迈克):本,本,帮忙!让我离开这里.本,快点,他们来了!让我离开这里.本,快点,让我出去!快点,本……
00:21:54,500
Jason: Who's Hans? TV (Mike) Benny, Benny, help!Get me out of here.Benny, hurry, they're coming!Get me out of here.Benny, come on, get me out!Quick, Benny...